A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records FA015
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Russell Sage Foundation photographs, 1911-1959, undated; 1059; 1.3 Cubic Feet
  - Mrs. Sage - Philanthropies - Constitution Island, undated (Box 53, Folder 608)
  - Portraits - F. Emerson Andrews, undated (Box 53, Folder 609)
  - Portraits - Robert Atkinson, undated (Box 53, Folder 610)
  - Portraits - Leonard Ayres, undated (Box 53, Folder 611)
  - Portraits - Mabel Badcock, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 612)
  - Portraits - Lindsay Bradford, 1938 (Box 53, Folder 613)
  - Portraits - Orville Brim, undated (Box 53, Folder 614)
  - Portraits - James Brockway, undated (Box 53, Folder 615)
  - Portraits - Esther Brown, undated (Box 53, Folder 616)
  - Portraits - W. Randolf Burgess, 1920 (Box 53, Folder 617)
  - Portraits - Margaret Byington, 1913 (Box 53, Folder 618)
  - Portraits - John Campbell, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 619)
  - Portraits - Olive Campbell, undated (Box 53, Folder 619A)
  - Portraits - Joseph Chamberlain, undated (Box 53, Folder 620)
  - Portraits - Harry Chase, undated (Box 53, Folder 621)
  - Portraits - Joanna Colcord, undated (Box 53, Folder 622)
  - Portraits - Leonard Cottrell, undated (Box 53, Folder 623)
  - Portraits - Eli Debevoise, undated (Box 53, Folder 624)
  - Portraits - Johnston de Forest, undated (Box 53, Folder 625)
  - Portraits - Robert de Forest, undated (Box 53, Folder 626)
  - Portraits - Cleveland Dodge, undated (Box 53, Folder 627)
  - Portraits - Allan Eaton, undated (Box 53, Folder 628)
  - Portraits - John Finley, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 629)
  - Portraits - John Glenn, undated (Box 53, Folder 629A)
  - Portraits - Luther H. Gulick, 1913 (Box 53, Folder 630)
  - Portraits - Morris Hadley, undated (Box 53, Folder 631)
  - Portraits - Fred Hall, undated (Box 53, Folder 632)
  - Portraits - Arthur Ham, 1918 (Box 53, Folder 633)
  - Portraits - Lee Hanmer, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 634)
  - Portraits - Shelby Harrison, undated (Box 54, Folder 635)
  - Portraits - Hastings Hart, undated (Box 54, Folder 636)
  - Portraits - Leon Henderson, 1934 (Box 54, Folder 637)
  - Portraits - William Hodson, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 638)
  - Portraits - Donald Howard, undated (Box 54, Folder 639)
  - Portraits - Bertha F. Hulseman, undated (Box 54, Folder 640)
  - Portraits - Ralph Hurlin, undated (Box 54, Folder 641)
  - Portraits - Frederick Jenkins, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 642)
  - Portraits - Russell Kurtz, undated (Box 54, Folder 643)
  - Portraits - Julia Lathrop, undated (Box 54, Folder 644)
  - Portraits - Laura B. Lee, undated (Box 54, Folder 645)
  - Portraits - Robert MacIver, undated (Box 54, Folder 646)
  - Portraits - Francis H. McLean, 1911 (Box 54, Folder 647)
  - Portraits - Helen Moore, undated (Box 54, Folder 648)
  - Portraits - Dave Morris, Jr., undated (Box 54, Folder 649)
  - Portraits - Charles Norton, undated (Box 54, Folder 650)
  - Portraits - Rolf Nugent, undated (Box 54, Folder 651)
  - Portraits - Robert Ogden, undated (Box 54, Folder 652)
  - Portraits - Clarence Perry, undated (Box 54, Folder 653)
  - Portraits - Abby Pike, 1937 (Box 54, Folder 654)
  - Portraits - Zenas Potter, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 655)
  - Portraits - Lawson Purdy, 1932 (Box 54, Folder 656)
  - Portraits - Mrs. William B. Rice, undated (Box 54, Folder 657)
  - Portraits - Mary Richmond, undated (Box 54, Folder 658)
  - Portraits - Evart Grant Routzahn, undated (Box 54, Folder 659)
  - Portraits - Mary S. Routzahn, undated (Box 54, Folder 660)
  - Portraits - Russell Sage Foundation Staff (Groups), undated (Box 54, Folder 661)
  - Portraits - Oscar Ruebhausen, undated (Box 54, Folder 662)
  - Portraits - Margaret Sage, undated (Box 54, Folder 663)
  - Portraits - Russell Sage, undated (Box 54, Folder 664)
  - Portraits - Louisa Schuyler, undated (Box 54, Folder 665)
  - Portraits - Helen Gould Shepard, undated (Box 54, Folder 666)
  - Portraits - Mary van Kleeck, undated (Box 55, Folder 667)
  - Portraits - Alfred White, undated (Box 55, Folder 668)
  - Portraits - Harold White, undated (Box 55, Folder 669)
  - Portraits - Donald Young, undated (Box 55, Folder 670)
  - Russell Sage Institute of Pathology, undated (Box 55, Folder 671)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Building, undated (Box 55, Folder 672)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Building, undated (Box 55, Folder 673)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Building, undated (Box 55, Folder 674)
  - Sag Harbor, undated (Box 55, Folder 675)
  - Sewaren Improvement Company, undated (Box 55, Folder 676)
  - Southern Highland Division, undated (Box 55, Folder 677)
  - Susana Hospital, undated (Box 55, Folder 678)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 55, Folder 679)